(DOOR THUDDING)
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)
♪ MAKING MY WAY DOWNTOWN ♪
♪ WALKING FAST, FACES
PASS AND I'M HOMEBOUND ♪
♪ STARING BLANKLY AHEAD ♪
♪ JUST MAKING MY WAY ♪
♪ MAKING A WAY
THROUGH THE CROWD ♪
♪ AND I NEED YOU ♪
♪ AND I MISS YOU ♪
♪ AND NOW I WONDER ♪
♪ IF I COULD FALL INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ DO YOU THINK TIME
WOULD PASS ME BY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU KNOW I'D
WALK 1,000 MILES ♪
♪ IF I COULD JUST
SEE YOU TONIGHT ♪
♪ IT'S ALWAYS TIMES LIKE
THESE WHEN I THINK OF YOU ♪
♪ AND WONDER IF YOU
EVER THINK OF ME ♪
♪ 'CAUSE EVERYTHING'S SO
WRONG, AND I DON'T BELONG ♪
♪ LIVING IN YOUR
PRECIOUS MEMORY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I NEED YOU ♪
♪ AND I MISS YOU ♪
♪ AND NOW I WONDER ♪
♪ IF I COULD FALL INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ DO YOU THINK TIME
WOULD PASS ME BY ♪
♪ OH, 'CAUSE YOU KNOW
I'D WALK 1,000 MILES ♪
♪ IF I COULD JUST
SEE YOU TONIGHT ♪
♪ AND I, I DON'T
WANNA LET YOU KNOW ♪
♪ I, I DROWN IN YOUR MEMORY ♪
♪ I, I DON'T WANNA LET THIS GO ♪
♪ I, I DON'T ♪
♪ MAKING MY WAY DOWNTOWN ♪
♪ WALKING FAST, FACES
PASS AND I'M HOMEBOUND ♪
♪ STARING BLANKLY AHEAD,
JUST MAKING MY WAY ♪
♪ MAKING A WAY
THROUGH THE CROWD ♪
♪ AND I STILL NEED YOU ♪
♪ AND I STILL MISS YOU ♪
♪ AND NOW I WONDER ♪
♪ IF I COULD FALL INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ DO YOU THINK TIME
WOULD PASS US BY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU KNOW I'D
WALK 1,000 MILES ♪
♪ IF I COULD JUST
SEE YOU, OH, OH ♪
♪ IF I COULD FALL INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ DO YOU THINK TIME
WOULD PASS ME BY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU KNOW I'D
WALK 1,000 MILES ♪
♪ IF I COULD JUST SEE YOU ♪
♪ IF I COULD JUST
HOLD YOU ♪
♪ TONIGHT ♪
(GENTLE PIANO MUSIC)